The pet food industry has received unkind remarks as to the true origin of its ingredients for decades.
几十年来，宠物食品行业在原料的真正来源问题上一直饱受尖刻的非议。
Now the industry faces another source of criticism as a new book starts a debate about the environmental impact of owning a well-fed pet.
如今，随着一本新书引发了一场关于“养一只吃得好的宠物会对环境造成什么影响”的争论，这个行业又多了一个招致批评的缘由。
The New Scientist magazine, in a recent editorial, largely agreed with the book’s findings that some pets, due to the food they eat, have a surprisingly high “ecological footprint”, which is a way of quantifying human demand on the planet’s ecosystems using a measure called “global hectares”.
《新科学家》杂志在最近的一篇社论中基本认同这本书的研究结论：一些宠物由于所吃的食物，“生态足迹”高得出人意料。“生态足迹”是一种量化人类对地球生态系统需求的方法，所用的计量单位叫作“全球公顷”。
According to the authors of the book, “A shocking comparison is that in 2004, the average citizen of some poor countries had an eco-footprint of 0.76 hectares.
据这本书的作者称：“一个令人震惊的对比是：2004年，一些贫穷国家普通公民的生态足迹为0.76公顷。
The eco-footprint of a medium-sized dog is about 0.84 hectares, and that of a cat is about 0.15 hectares, almost the same as what is needed to run a small car.
一只中型犬的生态足迹约为0.84公顷，一只猫的约为0.15公顷，几乎和开一辆小汽车所需的一样多。
In a world where resources are already limited, can people really justify keeping pets that require more than some people do?”
在一个资源本已有限的世界里，人们饲养所需资源比一些人还多的宠物，真的说得过去吗？”
The authors of the book say that they were “genuinely surprised” when calculating the environmental impact of pets.
这本书的作者说，他们在计算宠物对环境的影响时“真的很吃惊”。
And some of the ideas they put forward to attenuate this are likely to shock some pet owners.
而他们为减轻这种影响提出的一些主张，很可能会让一些宠物主人震惊。
For example, the book suggests catching pests such as field mice and processing them into a “natural” cat food, or raising pets like chickens that provide both company and fresh eggs.
例如，书中建议捕捉田鼠之类的有害动物，把它们加工成“天然”猫粮；或者饲养像鸡这样既能作伴、又能提供新鲜鸡蛋的宠物。
When feeding a pet, however, owners are advised to favour pet foods made from chicken meat, which is less damaging to the environment than red meat and fish.
不过，在喂养宠物时，建议主人优先选择用鸡肉制成的宠物食品，因为鸡肉对环境的危害比红肉和鱼肉小。
As you might expect, the Pet Food Manufacturers Association (PFMA) puts up a spirited defence, arguing that the vast majority of meat and fish used in pet foods is of sufficient quality for human consumption but surplus to human needs.
或许不出你所料，宠物食品制造商协会（PFMA）进行了有力的辩护，称宠物食品中使用的肉和鱼绝大多数品质都足以供人类食用，只是超出了人类的需求。
“If we didn’t recycle animal by-products to sell, they might instead be abandoned and buried under the earth, which is not very green,” says the PFMA’s director.
“如果我们不把动物副产品回收利用起来出售，它们就可能会被丢弃、埋到地下，那可不怎么环保，”该协会的负责人说。
In addition, he points out that pets should not be judged just on their carbon footprint.
此外，他指出，不应该仅凭碳足迹来评判宠物。
“Our environment is greatly enriched by the part they play in our lives.
“宠物在我们生活中所起的作用极大地丰富了我们的环境。
Pets in the home inspire responsibility, encourage social awareness and have positive health benefits.”
家里的宠物能激发责任感，增强社会意识，还对健康有积极作用。”